Jump on that.
Isn't that like an ebizo?
Yes, that's it.
I drew a rough sketch, but it's not very good.
Oh! Nice!
It's not very good.
It's terrible!
What's the image?
It's like...
It's like a school uniform.
Basically, white is good.
And take it off.
After taking it off...
This is really messy, but...
After you take it off...
It's a little bit like summer.
A little bit of see-through fabric.
I wanted to make it a costume.
and I want to make it a men's collar costume.
I'm going to wear
I want to make this see-through one below and
I want to make a men's color on the bottom of this
I'd like to make the men's collar
on the shoulder like this.
Like this.
It's a little hard to show in this picture, but...
I like the skirt.
And the bottom is a little bit tacky.
But if you have some kind of white, kind of
I think it would be cute with some white, kinda rugged sneakers
I think it would be cute.
Okay, I understand.
I'll leave you with this.
Good morning.
If you draw me a picture, I'll just draw it.
Oh! Whoa.
It goes like this.
Got it.
Yes, I can do it like this.
It's all right.
Thank you very much.
I like this one, because I have to take the foot off.
Yes, sir.
How do you want me to do it?
Here you go.
I just thought of something.
It's kind of an adolescent kind of thing.
Like a commercial.
I thought it might be a good idea.
I just thought of it.
Like this.
Hmmm...
Like a little sparkle spinning in the back of the bag.
It's very easy to do.
It's like there's a sense of movement.
I see.
So, Corona.
Do you want this party case? I want this one.
Here you go.
Thank you very much.
How do you like it?
It's cute. Very pretty.
I'm very happy because it has a taste that I don't see very often.
I made the top a bit like a school run, and had the uniforms made to look like a cheerleading squad.
And since the FC tour is scheduled for summer, the sleeves will be summery and see-through, and the men will be in men's colors.
I'm getting hungry.
I'm not in the mood yet.
I wanted to make it look like youth. It's summer and the FC tour is coming up.
I wanted it to feel like the youth of summer vacation. It was good to convey that to the people in Iwate.
You have never received any offers?
No, I have not.
No?
No, I have not. No, I don't.
I'd love to.
I can't play it yet.
I can't play it.
It's like a sense of dynamism.
Your eyes are too weird.
Too weird eyes?
Too weird?
Yeah.
Not much has changed.
Do you want to turn the other cheek? Not anymore.
Eyes, eyes, eyes, eyes. Smile. That's right.
Not “poof”, “poof”, “poof”, “poof”.
It won't stop. It won't stop.
It won't stop?
It won't stop.
It's too much.
Blasé, yes.
Okay, we'll see you later,
Next up, training today,
It's hot and Youtube is very aggresive person,
law lo ices yo and so on.
I'm still in the market for a headbutt,
I'd be crazy if I did it.
I'm not sure if it's a good idea,
I'm not sure what to say.
It's difficult.
What is it?
Are you dancing with Jab?
Pan.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much. Thanks for all your hard work.
I was about to laugh when the camera caught me.
I'd go “gah!”.
I see.
I guess I'll just do two moves.
You know, when you're flying...
As you fly.
Shake your head.
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm close.
It's so good.
Look, look, look.
This close.
This much.
That's about right.
Can I jump that?
Jump like a prawn.
Oh, yes.
That's right.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Star.
Thank you.
I was sweating.
Sorry Ganon
Sorry for the wait
Thank you
Thank you very much.
My tour concept is...
I'm pulling down the word “youth” in a big way.
The word “youth” is one of the most important words in this tour.
There are many songs that fit the keyword “youth”.
I would like to make a variety of interesting setlists.
To be more specific...
As I said in the FC pledge video
I'd like to play songs that we haven't played as 13 members yet. We want to play a lot of songs that we haven't performed with 13 members.
I would like to play a lot of songs that are not performed by 13 members.
I'm going to fulfill my personal desire to play a lot of songs that have not been performed by 13 members.
And playboys, too.
I'm sure there are still a lot of people who want to hear that song.
If you want to hear this song or that song, please let me know.
If you want to listen to this song or that song, please let me know.
If you want to listen to this song, please comment on my fan club post.
I would appreciate it if you could comment on my fan club post or X.
Thank you very much!
I'd like to think of many other things
I'm sure we can come up with many other things for you to enjoy.
I hope we can create wonderful memories of youth in the summer together
I hope we can create wonderful memories of youth in summer together.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
What we haven't done completely
We've done more than 100 songs for sure.
That's right.
But even if you've done more than 100 songs...
I still have dozens of songs left.
That's amazing.
That's what I'm trying to say.
I've been thinking...
I want to play that song, but I haven't played it yet.
I have a lot of songs that I haven't played yet.
I'd like to play them.
Wouldn't you like to hear it?
Don't you want to hear it?
Yes!